'use strict';

const cardiacQuestionBank = [
	{ id: 1,
		question: "What is a normal adult resting heart rate?",
		choices: ["130 bpm", "60 - 100 bpm", "30 bpm", "There is no predictable range."],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[1] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	},
	{ id: 2,
		question: "Which classification of medication is not given for a cardiac indication?",
		choices: ["ACE Inhibitors", "Beta Blockers", "Diuretics", "Proton Pump Inhibitors"],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[3] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	},
	{ id: 3,
		question: "Which word(s) means the heart is beating faster than normal?",
		choices: ["Bradycardia", "Cardiac arrest", "Tachycardia", "None of the above"],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[2] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	},
	{ id: 4,
		question: "What is the correct sequence of actions when providing CPR?",
		choices: ["Perform compressions, check airway, give breaths", "Check airway, give breaths, perform compressions", "Give breaths, perform compressions, check airway", "None of the above"],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[0] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	},	
	{ id: 5,
		question: "A patient with congestive heart failure should avoid too much:",
		choices: ["Salt", "Pepper", "Salt-N-Pepa", "Garlic"],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[0] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	},
	{ id: 6,
		question: "A patient complaining of chest pain has been given one sublingual dose of nitro gylcerin. If he continues to have chest pain, when can the next dose of nitro by given?",
		choices: ["Only one dose can be given", "5 minutes after first dose", "4 hours after first dose", "As soon as needed"],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[1] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	},
	{ id: 7,
		question: "Fill in the blank: a left _______ assist device helps a weakened heart pump blood to the rest of the body.",
		choices: ["Suction", "Coronary", "Ventricular", "And right"],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[2] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	},
	{ id: 8,
		question: "Following oxygenation by the lungs blood flows where?",
		choices: ["Right Ventricle", "Left Atria", "Left Ventricle", "Right big toe"],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[1] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	},
	{ id: 9,
		question: "A patient with atrial fibrillation may need to have which procedure?",
		choices: ["An ablation", "A hysterectomy", "An appendectomy", "A coronary bypass"],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[0] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	},
	{ id: 10,
		question: "Home is where the ______ is.",
		choices: ["Money", "X-Box", "Food", "Heart"],
		correctAnswer: function() { return this.choices[3] },
		answered: false,
		correct: null	}
]
//correctAnswer key is a function to use 'this' self reference to choices array

const cardiacQuestions = {count: 1};